[
    {
        "question": "Rejoice greatly, Daughter Zion! Shout, Daughter Jerusalem! See, your king comes to you, righteous and having salvation, lowly and riding on a donkey, on a colt, the foal of a donkey.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 9:9",
        "rank": "739"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"And I will pour out on the house of David and the inhabitants of Jerusalem a spirit of grace and supplication. They will look on me, the one they have pierced, and they will mourn for him as one mourns for an only child, and grieve bitterly for him as one grieves for a firstborn son.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 12:10",
        "rank": "771"
    },
    {
        "question": "So he said to me, \"This is the word of the LORD to Zerubbabel: 'Not by might nor by power, but by my Spirit,' says the LORD Almighty.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 4:6",
        "rank": "1,578"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"The LORD was very angry with your ancestors.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:2",
        "rank": "1,608"
    },
    {
        "question": "On that day his feet will stand on the Mount of Olives, east of Jerusalem, and the Mount of Olives will be split in two from east to west, forming a great valley, with half of the mountain moving north and half moving south.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 14:4",
        "rank": "2,355"
    },
    {
        "question": "Therefore tell the people: This is what the LORD Almighty says: 'Return to me,' declares the LORD Almighty, 'and I will return to you,' says the LORD Almighty.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:3",
        "rank": "2,383"
    },
    {
        "question": "I will take away the chariots from Ephraim and the warhorses from Jerusalem, and the battle bow will be broken. He will proclaim peace to the nations. His rule will extend from sea to sea and from the River to the ends of the earth.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 9:10",
        "rank": "2,758"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do not be like your ancestors, to whom the earlier prophets proclaimed: This is what the LORD Almighty says: 'Turn from your evil ways and your evil practices.' But they would not listen or pay attention to me, declares the LORD.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:4",
        "rank": "3,012"
    },
    {
        "question": "A day of the LORD is coming, Jerusalem, when your possessions will be plundered and divided up within your very walls.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 14:1",
        "rank": "3,053"
    },
    {
        "question": "I told them, \"If you think it best, give me my pay; but if not, keep it.\" So they paid me thirty pieces of silver.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 11:12",
        "rank": "3,054"
    },
    {
        "question": "The LORD will be king over the whole earth. On that day there will be one LORD, and his name the only name.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 14:9",
        "rank": "3,411"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"But did not my words and my decrees, which I commanded my servants the prophets, overtake your ancestors? \"Then they repented and said, 'The LORD Almighty has done to us what our ways and practices deserve, just as he determined to do.\"\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:6",
        "rank": "3,503"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where are your ancestors now? And the prophets, do they live forever?",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:5",
        "rank": "3,564"
    },
    {
        "question": "The clan of the house of Levi and their wives, the clan of Shimei and their wives",
        "answer": "Zechariah 12:13",
        "rank": "3,599"
    },
    {
        "question": "On the twenty-fourth day of the eleventh month, the month of Shebat, in the second year of Darius, the word of the LORD came to the prophet Zechariah son of Berekiah, the son of Iddo.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:7",
        "rank": "3,632"
    },
    {
        "question": "A similar plague will strike the horses and mules, the camels and donkeys, and all the animals in those camps.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 14:15",
        "rank": "3,683"
    },
    {
        "question": "This is what the LORD Almighty says: \"Now hear these words, 'Let your hands be strong so that the temple may be built.' This is also what the prophets said who were present when the foundation was laid for the house of the LORD Almighty.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 8:9",
        "rank": "3,737"
    },
    {
        "question": "And all the rest of the clans and their wives.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 12:14",
        "rank": "3,748"
    },
    {
        "question": "The angel said to those who were standing before him, \"Take off his filthy clothes.\" Then he said to Joshua, \"See, I have taken away your sin, and I will put fine garments on you.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 3:4",
        "rank": "3,842"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the man standing among the myrtle trees explained, \"They are the ones the LORD has sent to go throughout the earth.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:10",
        "rank": "3,981"
    },
    {
        "question": "And they reported to the angel of the LORD who was standing among the myrtle trees, \"We have gone throughout the earth and found the whole world at rest and in peace.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:11",
        "rank": "3,988"
    },
    {
        "question": "I asked, \"What are these, my lord?\" The angel who was talking with me answered, \"I will show you what they are.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:9",
        "rank": "4,002"
    },
    {
        "question": "He answered, \"Do you not know what these are?\" \"No, my lord,\" I replied.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 4:5",
        "rank": "4,025"
    },
    {
        "question": "As for you, because of the blood of my covenant with you, I will free your prisoners from the waterless pit.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 9:11",
        "rank": "4,049"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the angel who was speaking to me said, \"Proclaim this word: This is what the LORD Almighty says: 'I am very jealous for Jerusalem and Zion,\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:14",
        "rank": "4,059"
    },
    {
        "question": "While the angel who was speaking to me was leaving, another angel came to meet him",
        "answer": "Zechariah 2:3",
        "rank": "4,110"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the angel of the LORD said, \"LORD Almighty, how long will you withhold mercy from Jerusalem and from the towns of Judah, which you have been angry with these seventy years?\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:12",
        "rank": "4,146"
    },
    {
        "question": "So the LORD spoke kind and comforting words to the angel who talked with me.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:13",
        "rank": "4,211"
    },
    {
        "question": "And the word of the LORD came again to Zechariah:",
        "answer": "Zechariah 7:8",
        "rank": "4,297"
    },
    {
        "question": "And I am very angry with the nations that feel secure. I was only a little angry, but they added to the calamity.'",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:15",
        "rank": "4,298"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"\"Proclaim further: This is what the LORD Almighty says: 'My towns will again overflow with prosperity, and the LORD will again comfort Zion and choose Jerusalem.\"\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:17",
        "rank": "4,348"
    },
    {
        "question": "They will pass through the sea of trouble; the surging sea will be subdued and all the depths of the Nile will dry up. Assyria's pride will be brought down and Egypt's scepter will pass away.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 10:11",
        "rank": "4,352"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then I looked up, and there before me were four horns.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:18",
        "rank": "4,443"
    },
    {
        "question": "I asked, \"What are these coming to do?\" He answered, \"These are the horns that scattered Judah so its people could not raise their heads, but the craftsmen have come to terrify them and throw down these horns of the nations who lifted up their horns against the land of Judah to scatter its people.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:21",
        "rank": "4,467"
    },
    {
        "question": "Before that time there were no wages for people or animals. People could not go about their business safely because of conflicts, since I had turned them all against each other.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 8:10",
        "rank": "4,487"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Therefore, this is what the LORD says: 'I will return to Jerusalem with mercy, and there my house will be rebuilt. And the measuring line will be stretched out over Jerusalem,' declares the LORD Almighty.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:16",
        "rank": "4,503"
    },
    {
        "question": "When the powerful horses went out, they were straining to go throughout the earth. And he said, \"Go throughout the earth!\" So they went throughout the earth.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 6:7",
        "rank": "4,611"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the LORD showed me four craftsmen.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:20",
        "rank": "4,640"
    },
    {
        "question": "I will strengthen them in the LORD and in his name they will live securely,\" declares the LORD.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 10:12",
        "rank": "4,746"
    },
    {
        "question": "I asked the angel who was speaking to me, \"What are these?\" He answered me, \"These are the horns that scattered Judah, Israel and Jerusalem.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:19",
        "rank": "4,878"
    },
    {
        "question": "But now I will not deal with the remnant of this people as I did in the past,\" declares the LORD Almighty.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 8:11",
        "rank": "5,105"
    },
    {
        "question": "And the LORD said to me, \"Throw it to the potter\" \u2013 the handsome price at which they valued me! So I took the thirty pieces of silver and threw them to the potter at the house of the LORD.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 11:13",
        "rank": "5,170"
    },
    {
        "question": "Return to your fortress, you prisoners of hope; even now I announce that I will restore twice as much to you.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 9:12",
        "rank": "5,279"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then he called to me, \"Look, those going toward the north country have given my Spirit rest in the land of the north.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 6:8",
        "rank": "5,280"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then I said, \"Put a clean turban on his head.\" So they put a clean turban on his head and clothed him, while the angel of the LORD stood by.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 3:5",
        "rank": "5,357"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"This is what the LORD Almighty said: 'Administer true justice; show mercy and compassion to one another.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 7:9",
        "rank": "5,383"
    },
    {
        "question": "And said to him: \"Run, tell that young man, 'Jerusalem will be a city without walls because of the great number of people and animals in it.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 2:4",
        "rank": "5,468"
    },
    {
        "question": "I asked, \"What is it?\" He replied, \"It is a basket.\" And he added, \"This is the iniquity of the people throughout the land.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 5:6",
        "rank": "5,596"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then I broke my second staff called Union, breaking the family bond between Judah and Israel.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 11:14",
        "rank": "5,631"
    },
    {
        "question": "If any of the peoples of the earth do not go up to Jerusalem to worship the King, the LORD Almighty, they will have no rain.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 14:17",
        "rank": "5,643"
    },
    {
        "question": "This is what the LORD Almighty says: \"Just as I had determined to bring disaster on you and showed no pity when your ancestors angered me,\" says the LORD Almighty",
        "answer": "Zechariah 8:14",
        "rank": "5,851"
    },
    {
        "question": "The word of the LORD came to me:",
        "answer": "Zechariah 6:9",
        "rank": "5,852"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"The seed will grow well, the vine will yield its fruit, the ground will produce its crops, and the heavens will drop their dew. I will give all these things as an inheritance to the remnant of this people.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 8:12",
        "rank": "5,959"
    },
    {
        "question": "And I myself will be a wall of fire around it,' declares the LORD, 'and I will be its glory within.'",
        "answer": "Zechariah 2:5",
        "rank": "6,103"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"\"What are you, mighty mountain? Before Zerubbabel you will become level ground. Then he will bring out the capstone to shouts of 'God bless it! God bless it!\"\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 4:7",
        "rank": "6,227"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do not oppress the widow or the fatherless, the foreigner or the poor. Do not plot evil against each other.'",
        "answer": "Zechariah 7:10",
        "rank": "6,457"
    },
    {
        "question": "I will bend Judah as I bend my bow and fill it with Ephraim. I will rouse your sons, Zion, against your sons, Greece, and make you like a warrior's sword.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 9:13",
        "rank": "6,477"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Listen, High Priest Joshua, you and your associates seated before you, you who are symbolic of things to come: I am going to bring my servant, the Branch.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 3:8",
        "rank": "6,478"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the LORD said to me, \"Take again the equipment of a foolish shepherd.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 11:15",
        "rank": "6,589"
    },
    {
        "question": "See, the stone I have set in front of Joshua! There are seven eyes on that one stone, and I will engrave an inscription on it,' says the LORD Almighty, 'and I will remove the sin of this land in a single day.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 3:9",
        "rank": "6,590"
    },
    {
        "question": "The angel of the LORD gave this charge to Joshua:",
        "answer": "Zechariah 3:6",
        "rank": "6,591"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Come! Come! Flee from the land of the north,\" declares the LORD, \"for I have scattered you to the four winds of heaven,\" declares the LORD.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 2:6",
        "rank": "6,650"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"But they refused to pay attention; stubbornly they turned their backs and covered their ears.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 7:11",
        "rank": "6,767"
    },
    {
        "question": "If the Egyptian people do not go up and take part, they will have no rain. The LORD will bring on them the plague he inflicts on the nations that do not go up to celebrate the Festival of Tabernacles.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 14:18",
        "rank": "6,941"
    },
    {
        "question": "It is he who will build the temple of the LORD, and he will be clothed with majesty and will sit and rule on his throne. And he will be a priest on his throne. And there will be harmony between the two.'",
        "answer": "Zechariah 6:13",
        "rank": "6,942"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"This is what the LORD Almighty says: 'If you will walk in obedience to me and keep my requirements, then you will govern my house and have charge of my courts, and I will give you a place among these standing here.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 3:7",
        "rank": "7,075"
    },
    {
        "question": "For this is what the LORD Almighty says: \"After the Glorious One has sent me against the nations that have plundered you \u2013 for whoever touches you touches the apple of his eye \u2013 \"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 2:8",
        "rank": "7,111"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the word of the LORD came to me:",
        "answer": "Zechariah 4:8",
        "rank": "7,176"
    },
    {
        "question": "A prophecy: The word of the LORD is against the land of Hadrak and will come to rest on Damascus \u2013  for the eyes of all people and all the tribes of Israel are on the LORD \u2013",
        "answer": "Zechariah 9:1",
        "rank": "7,196"
    },
    {
        "question": "He replied, \"To the country of Babylonia to build a house for it. When it is ready, the basket will be set there in its place.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 5:11",
        "rank": "7,393"
    },
    {
        "question": "For I am going to raise up a shepherd over the land who will not care for the lost, or seek the young, or heal the injured, or feed the healthy, but will eat the meat of the choice sheep, tearing off their hooves.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 11:16",
        "rank": "7,622"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the cover of lead was raised, and there in the basket sat a woman!",
        "answer": "Zechariah 5:7",
        "rank": "7,669"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Who dares despise the day of small things, since the seven eyes of the LORD that range throughout the earth will rejoice when they see the chosen capstone in the hand of Zerubbabel?\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 4:10",
        "rank": "7,670"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Woe to the worthless shepherd, who deserts the flock! May the sword strike his arm and his right eye! May his arm be completely withered, his right eye totally blinded!\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 11:17",
        "rank": "7,698"
    },
    {
        "question": "During the night I had a vision, and there before me was a man mounted on a red horse. He was standing among the myrtle trees in a ravine. Behind him were red, brown and white horses.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 1:8",
        "rank": "7,712"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Shout and be glad, Daughter Zion. For I am coming, and I will live among you,\" declares the LORD.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 2:10",
        "rank": "7,736"
    },
    {
        "question": "How attractive and beautiful they will be! Grain will make the young men thrive, and new wine the young women.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 9:17",
        "rank": "7,832"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Just as you, Judah and Israel, have been a curse among the nations, so I will save you, and you will be a blessing. Do not be afraid, but let your hands be strong.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 8:13",
        "rank": "8,142"
    },
    {
        "question": "They made their hearts as hard as flint and would not listen to the law or to the words that the LORD Almighty had sent by his Spirit through the earlier prophets. So the LORD Almighty was very angry.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 7:12",
        "rank": "8,143"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"In that day each of you will invite your neighbor to sit under your vine and fig tree,' declares the LORD Almighty.\"\"\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 3:10",
        "rank": "8,144"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the LORD will appear over them; his arrow will flash like lightning. The Sovereign LORD will sound the trumpet; he will march in the storms of the south",
        "answer": "Zechariah 9:14",
        "rank": "8,177"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"The hands of Zerubbabel have laid the foundation of this temple; his hands will also complete it. Then you will know that the LORD Almighty has sent me to you.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 4:9",
        "rank": "8,205"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"And many peoples and powerful nations will come to Jerusalem to seek the LORD Almighty and to entreat him.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 8:22",
        "rank": "8,365"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tell him this is what the LORD Almighty says: 'Here is the man whose name is the Branch, and he will branch out from his place and build the temple of the LORD.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 6:12",
        "rank": "8,366"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Come, Zion! Escape, you who live in Daughter Babylon!\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 2:7",
        "rank": "8,435"
    },
    {
        "question": "And the LORD Almighty will shield them. They will destroy and overcome with slingstones. They will drink and roar as with wine; they will be full like a bowl used for sprinkling the corners of the altar.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 9:15",
        "rank": "8,504"
    },
    {
        "question": "He said, \"This is wickedness,\" and he pushed her back into the basket and pushed the lead cover down over its mouth.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 5:8",
        "rank": "8,709"
    },
    {
        "question": "On that day HOLY TO THE LORD will be inscribed on the bells of the horses, and the cooking pots in the LORD's house will be like the sacred bowls in front of the altar.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 14:20",
        "rank": "8,747"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"so now I have determined to do good again to Jerusalem and Judah. Do not be afraid.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 8:15",
        "rank": "8,782"
    },
    {
        "question": "The LORD their God will save his people on that day as a shepherd saves his flock. They will sparkle in his land like jewels in a crown.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 9:16",
        "rank": "8,859"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Take silver and gold from the exiles Heldai, Tobijah and Jedaiah, who have arrived from Babylon. Go the same day to the house of Josiah son of Zephaniah.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 6:10",
        "rank": "8,860"
    },
    {
        "question": "I will surely raise my hand against them so that their slaves will plunder them. Then you will know that the LORD Almighty has sent me.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 2:9",
        "rank": "8,861"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then I asked the angel, \"What are these two olive trees on the right and the left of the lampstand?\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 4:11",
        "rank": "8,970"
    },
    {
        "question": "On that day, when all the nations of the earth are gathered against her, I will make Jerusalem an immovable rock for all the nations. All who try to move it will injure themselves.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 12:3",
        "rank": "9,154"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"\"I scattered them with a whirlwind among all the nations, where they were strangers. The land they left behind them was so desolate that no one traveled through it. This is how they made the pleasant land desolate.\"\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 7:14",
        "rank": "9,253"
    },
    {
        "question": "The LORD will inherit Judah as his portion in the holy land and will again choose Jerusalem.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 2:12",
        "rank": "9,421"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ask the LORD for rain in the springtime; it is the LORD who sends the thunderstorms. He gives showers of rain to all people, and plants of the field to everyone.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 10:1",
        "rank": "9,459"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"When I called, they did not listen; so when they called, I would not listen,' says the LORD Almighty.\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 7:13",
        "rank": "9,505"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"This is what the LORD Almighty says: \"In those days ten people from all languages and nations will take firm hold of one Jew by the hem of his robe and say, 'Let us go with you, because we have heard that God is with you.\"\"",
        "answer": "Zechariah 8:23",
        "rank": "9,610"
    },
    {
        "question": "Then the angel who talked with me returned and wakened me, as one is wakened from sleep.",
        "answer": "Zechariah 4:1",
        "rank": "9,611"
    }
]